I would like you to listen to what I have to say now, because I will try to explain why we get high current prices in Norway.
The first principle everyone must understand is that the current always goes where the price is highest.
That is the main principle.
The second thing we must understand is that all the 17 cables that go out of Norway can, in theory, export half a part of the electricity we use in Norway in the course of a year.
And only the two last cables to Germany and Serbia, double the export capacity from Sørenøge.
But this will never happen, I will not guarantee.
This will not happen that we export half a part of our electricity.
In fact, we do not need to export a single drop of water power, because the current price in Norway will not be as high as in Germany.
Not a single drop of water power.
And here, I feel now, here comes the explanation.
I'll take it in four, Trin.
Trin 1 is that everyone who produces power, and everyone who buys power, or wants to buy power, meets at a market place.
It can, for example, be called a Nordpol.
And there it is German, Swedish, Danish, Norwegian, but many people.
Trin 2 is that the power producers, this is the main principle, they sell of course to those who pay the most.
And if that is German, then a part of the current goes to Germany.
Trin 3 is that the Norwegian power companies, and we know them, we know them.
They are called Fjordkraft, Norge Seneggi, Tibber, and so on.
Yes, they have agreed with us, Norway, to use, that they will give us electricity, die around.
And then they have most of our spot price numbers.
What that actually means, is that we have given the power companies permission to buy electricity for us for an unlimited price.
So when Norwegian power companies know that they can get a higher price abroad than in Norway,
and they know that we have big cables that make them export a lot,
then they put the price on their water power high, because they know that the Norwegian power companies,
they want to have this power as it is, and they want to pay what it costs, to make Germany and Britain.
And Trin 4 here, is that we have to use, we have to accept this price as this system is,
but if the price is very high, then we begin to save.
So, the power companies do their job, they just have to pay as much for the water as possible.
The electricity companies also do their job.
They are actually just going to give us the electricity, no matter what the price is.
And we use it, we still do our job.
We buy power, we buy the electricity we need, and we begin to save if it gets too expensive.
All this can happen, except that it basically goes from Norway to the abroad.
Yes, it's too many now.